

Professional with 12+ years of experience. Has strong background in business development, project management, marketing, customer relations and planning.

Since 2005 involved in different NGO's, was performing as program coordinator, trainer and facilitator. Since 2018 certificated trainer for Youth in Action and Erasmus+ programs funded by EU.

MIRISMAYIL RZAYEV

CONTACT

+994555150298

✓ mirismayil.rzayev@yahoo.com

Sumqayit, Azerbaijan

EDUCATION

2010 - 2012

ISM UNIVERSITY OF

MANAGEMENT AND ECONOMICS

Marketing and Management Vilnus, Lithuania

2005 - 2009

ACADEMY OF PUBLIC

ADMINISTRATION UNDER THE

PRESIDENT OF THE RA

International Relations Baku, Azerbaijan

SKILLS

- Analytical skills
- Big picture view
- Budgets controlling
- Easy adaptive and flexibility skills
- Campaigns targeting and mapping
- Communication skills
- Decision making
- Details oriented
- Goal oriented
- Mentoring skills
- Market research skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

 PRODUCT MANAGER Avrora LLC 	11/2022 - up to date
BUSINESS CONSULTANT Forte Fashion Retail	01/2022 - 11/2022
MARKETING MANAGER Lactalis Caspi	01/2021 - 11/2021
CATEGORY MANAGER Delta Group	02/2020 - 09/2020
 TRAADE MARKETING MANAGER STP 	01/2019 - 01/2020
 TRADE MARKETING MANAGER Avrora LLC 	01/2017 - 10/2018
 BRAND MANAGER Azersun Holding 	02/2014 - 11/2017
 BRAND MANAGER ASSISTANT Delta Group 	11/2012 - 02/2014

CERTIFICATIONS

Changes Management Ali M	12/2024
Al in Data Analysis	08/2024
Enes Eryarsoy	
 Visioner Leadership 	10/2023
Burçin Doğru	
Agility and Creativity	10/2023
Çağlayan Aktaş	
 Marketing and Digital Innovations 	05/2023
AIIM	
 Value Generation and MarCom 	07/2021
Lactalis International	
 Innovations and Sales Strategies 	05/2021
Lactalis International	
Digital Marketing Conference	12/2018
Facemark	

SKILLS

- Planning skills
- Problem solving skills
- Project management skills
- Strategy designing
- Team leader skills
- Trainer skills (TOT)

LANGUAGES

- Azerbaijani (Native)
- English (TOEFL İBT 95)
- Rusian (Fluent)
- Turkish (Intermediade)

CERTIFICATIONS

Business Negotiations	11/2017
Business Ring	
Azersun Marketing Academy	05/2016
Azersun Holding	
 Marketing Kingdom Baku 	04/2015
Facemark	
 Sales Strategies of Successful Brands 	03/2014
ILT Academy	

REFERENCES

Yusif Rzayev	Elgun Khalilov	Elchin Zeynalov
Azersun Holding	Avrora LLC	Baku Textile Fabric
Head of Department	Head of Division	Director
+994772190877	+994707194969	+994502633032